

MYKHAILO TSYRTSAKI

STUDENT IN LAPLAND UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

ABOUT ME

My name is Mykhailo (Finnish version - Mika), I moved to Finland due to the war in my country. I was born on November 10th, 2004. I am currently a student at the Lapland University of Applied Sciences, majoring in Machine Learning and Data Engineering.

I have experience in a system administration, organization of events and teamwork, volunteering, graphic design, social network administration

SKILLS

- Programming languages: Python, JS, Java
- Communication skills (communication with people of different ages, positions and nationalities)
- Event organization and teamwork skills (organized motorcycle and auto events, and was also the organizer of a small team of programmers)
- Administration of social networks (was the administrator of small news channels, as well as online stores)
- Knowledge of Ukrainian(native), Russian(native) and English(B2) languages

PERSONAL RECOMMENDATIONS

Jarkko Rönkkö Former colleague and mentor at SPR Rovaniemi +358 40 4450848

HOW TO CONTACT ME

Phone number: +358 46 5517962 Email: tsyrtsaki.m@gmail.com Telegram: @tsyrtsakim Instagram: @tsyrtsaki.m LinkedIn: @tsyrtsaki

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Social network administration 02.2019-02.2022
- System Administrator 05.2021-08.2021
- Organization of events 2019-02.2022
- Graphic designer 2019-2022(freelance)
- Volunteer at the Rovaniemi SPR 06.2022-09.2022

EDUCATION

Student of the Lapland University of applied sciences

Specialty - Machine Learning and Data Engineering Since 01.09.2022

High school - Author's school of N.P. Guzik 2020-2022

INTERESTS

- Communication with people
- Event organization
- Programming
- Photo
- Listening music